justmeans.com 2019-08-06

# Privacy Policy

                                   Privacy Policy
                              Last Updated August 7, 2018
3BL Media is your go-to partner for shaping, sharing and strategically
targeting purpose-driven stories, initiatives and ideas with the people who
matter.
3BL Media, LLC (“3BL Media”) recognizes the importance of ensuring each
customer, visitor, client and user’s privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to all of
the services provided by 3BL Media and subsidiaries, including, but not
limited to, website services, content distribution, including, but not limited to
Internet clips, press releases, blogs, webcasts, podcasts, tweets, and other
electronic media (collectively referred to as the “Services”).
This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, protect and share
information about you that we obtain when you use our Services or otherwise
communicate with us. Our “Services” include (i) our US websites that post this
Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Websites”); (ii) other online products and
services provided by us through our Websites; and (iii) databases, distribution
services, articles, surveys, newsletters, webinars, media monitoring, and/or
analytic reports.
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand how we will treat your
information before you start to use our Services or communicate with us
about them. By using our Services, or communicating with us about them,
you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy
Policy, including any updates and amendments. If you do not agree to the
terms of this Privacy Policy, you must not access or use our Services or
communicate with us about them. Your use of our Services and any dispute
over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and any applicable Terms of
Use, and/or any other agreements. In the event that the provisions of any
such agreements differ from or conflict with the provisions of this Privacy
Policy, the applicable terms or agreement will apply.
How We Collect Information from You
The manner in which we use information about you varies depending upon
the capacity in which you visit our sites. For example, if you simply visit our
pages for news and do not register, we may not know who you are and do
not intend to collect information which identifies you. However, if you are
using the subscription-only areas routinely to represent a client company, we
may note and monitor how the Service is being utilized.
3BL Media requires registration for certain Services and our website may
contain order forms for other Services. In order to provide our Services to you,
we may ask you for business information (such as name of company and

industry), contact information (name and email address), financial
information (such as account or credit card numbers), and demographic
information (such as location information).
We may use cookies or other tracking mechanisms to gather and record
information to helps us operate and provide our Services to you. A cookie is a
small file of information which we place on your browser. That cookie then
communicates with our servers on return visits and allows us to recognize
your personal computer. We associate a cookie with information that
identifies you only if you use the automatic recognition capabilities on
restricted areas. Our log servers collect standard web information about visits
and system capabilities as you access and use the web pages covered by this
policy.
This information includes, without limitation:
    •  Information about the systems and device(s) you use to access our
       Services, including MAC address, IP address, browser type and version,
       time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating
       system and platform, device type, and device identifiers;
    •  Information about your visits to the Websites, including the full URL
       clickstream to, through and from the Websites (including date and
       time);
    •  Information about your use of our mobile apps, including the
       information you view in our mobile apps and the date and time you
       view it;
    •  Information to facilitate your use of our Services (including to provide
       access to third-party websites and services), such as URL requests,
       destination IP addresses, or device configuration details; and
    •  Pages you view or search for, page response times, download errors,
       length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as
       scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), your engagement with certain
       variable/dynamic elements of a page and methods used to browse
       away from the page.
If you decline to have us collect such information (for example, by disabling
cookies; see Cookies & Other Tracking Mechanisms below), we may not be
able to provide our Services to you.
Information We Collect about You from Third Parties
Our Services may also, from time to time, contain links to and from social or
other media platforms. You may choose to connect with us through a social
media platform and when you do, and to the extent available, we may collect
additional information from you, such as your user names, profile picture,
contact information, contact list, and the profile pictures of your contacts,

through the social media platform. Please be advised that social media
platforms may also collect information from you. We do not have control over
the collection, use and sharing practices of social media platforms and
encourage you to review their usage and disclosure policies and practices,
including the data security practices, before using the social media platforms.
We may combine the information we collect about you from the various
sources described above.
Information About Other Individuals
If you give us information on behalf of someone else, you confirm that the
other person has appointed you to act on his/her behalf and has agreed that
you can provide the information. Furthermore, you confirm that you informed
the other person about the content of this Privacy Policy, by providing
him/her with a current version of it.
How Your Information May Be Used
We may use any information we collect, including personal information and
technical information, as described to you at the time of collection, for the
following purposes:
    •  Services: Operating, protecting and improving our Services (e.g.,
       administration, troubleshooting, managing account access, protecting
       security); evaluating our Services; developing new features, products, or
       services; and for other customer service and support purposes.
    •  Experience: Personalizing the information and content we display to
       you, including marketing, promotional and sponsored content and
       advertising within the Services.
    •  Marketing and communications: Contacting you directly about your
       use of an account or Service for which you are registered; providing you
       with information about products or services, from us or third parties
       that may interest you; serving advertisements to you; and responding
       to your requests, feedback or questions.
    •  Metrics: Researching and analyzing how you interact with our Services,
       including to monitor usage and activity trends and for statistical
       purposes; creating reports for customers that may include both
       aggregate trends and the organizations that are viewing their content,
       or accessing our Services or customer websites or otherwise using our
       Services; and measuring or understanding the effectiveness of content,
       communications, Website visits, web traffic, our Services, or advertising
       we or our customers serve to you and other customers like you, and to
       deliver relevant advertising to you and other customers like you.
    •  Compliance: Complying with laws, regulations and requests from law
       enforcement or other governmental entities; carrying out our

      obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts; and using
      as evidence in litigation.
   •  Protection: Protecting the safety, rights or property of 3BL Media, LLC,
      customers, end users, or any third party; investigating, preventing or
      otherwise addressing activity that 3BL Media, LLC, in its sole discretion,
      may consider to be or pose a risk of being, an illegal, unethical, or legally
      questionable activity.
We may also create aggregate or anonymous information about your and
other users’ use of our Services for purposes similar to those listed above.
How Your Information May Be Shared
We will not sell your personal information or share your personal information
with third parties for the third party’s own direct marketing purposes.
We may share any information, including personal information as follows:
   •  With our subsidiaries and affiliates, including any future subsidiaries or
      affiliates;
   •  With our service providers and sub-contractors to the extent
      reasonably necessary to enable us provide our Services (e.g., we use a
      third-party platform for e-mail and cannot communicate with you
      without disclosing your e-mail address to our third-party e-mail
      provider);
   •  With a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture,
      restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of any
      of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy,
      liquidation or similar proceeding, including during planning or
      negotiations of such sale or transfer;
   •  With a third party with whom we must legally share information about
      you;
   •  With the company or organization you represent upon their request;
   •  With you or other third parties with your express consent;
   •  To comply with any court order, valid subpoena, law or legal process,
      including to respond to any government or regulatory request;
   •  To investigate potential unauthorized access or misuse of our Services
      or otherwise enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements;
   •  To protect our assets or rights, including for billing and collection
      purposes;
   •  If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights,
      property, or safety of 3BL Media, LLC, our customers or others, including
      exchanging information with other companies and organizations for
      the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction; and
   •  With any other entity disclosed by us when you provide the
      information.

We may also share aggregate or anonymous data for marketing, advertising,
research, compliance, or other purposes.
In the event that we receive a request from a governmental entity to provide
it with your personal information, we will take reasonable attempts to notify
you of such request, to the extent reasonably possible and legally permissible.
Cookies & Other Tracking Mechanisms
We may use cookies, beacons and similar technologies, now or in the future,
to support the functionality or track usage of our Services. This provides a
better experience when you use our Services and allows us to improve our
Services.
    •  Browser Cookies: A browser cookie is a small file placed on the hard
       drive of your computer. That cookie then communicates with servers,
       ours or those of other companies that we authorize to collect data for
       us, and allows recognition of your device. You may use the tools
       available on your computer or other device to set your browser to
       refuse or disable all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when
       cookies are being sent. However, if you refuse or disable all browser
       cookies, you may be unable to access certain parts of our Websites or
       use certain features or functionality of our Services.
    •  Flash Cookies: Certain features of our Services may use local stored
       objects called flash cookies to collect and store information about your
       preferences and navigation to, from and on our Websites. We also
       include cookies in our third-party hosted video players to count the
       number of unique viewers who see a customer’s video press release
       and to provide aggregate reporting. Flash cookies are not managed by
       the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. To learn
       how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player
       settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse Flash cookies,
       please note that some parts of our Services may be inaccessible or may
       not function properly.
    •  Web Beacons: Our Services may contain small electronic files known
       as web beacons (also referred to as clear GIFs, pixel tags, tracking pixels
       and single-pixel GIFs) that permit us to, for example, count users who
       have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other website-
       related statistics. Web beacons in e-mail marketing campaigns, press
       releases or other types of communications or content allow us to track
       your responses and your interests in our content, offerings and web
       pages. We may use web beacons and/or other tracking technologies to
       collect information about you when you interact with our Services, e-
       mails, press releases or other types of communications or content,
       including information about your browsing and purchasing behavior.

   •  Analytics Services: We or our affiliates also use a variety of web
      analytics services. Such web analytics services use cookies and similar
      technologies to analyze how users use the domains. The information
      generated about domain usage (including your shortened IP address)
      is transmitted to the web analytics services. This information is used to
      evaluate visitors’ use of the domain, compile statistical reports on
      domain activity, and provide other services related to the Site and
      Internet use. Such services may also collect information about domain
      visitors’ use of other websites.
Do Not Track Disclosure
Some browsers support a “Do Not Track” feature, which is intended to be a
signal to websites that you do not wish to be tracked across different
websites you visit. Our Services do not change the way they operate based
upon detection of a Do Not Track or similar signal.
Your Choices
   •  Opting out of marketing communications. You may receive certain
      promotional or informational communications from us. Where required
      by law, promotional communications will be sent only with your
      consent. You can opt out of promotional e-mails at any time by
      following the instructions at the bottom of the e-mails. Please note that
      certain e-mails may be necessary for the operation of our Services. You
      may, however, continue to receive these e-mails relating to your
      account or our Services, if appropriate, even if you unsubscribe from our
      optional communications.
   •  Opting out of behavioral advertising. You may opt out of many third-
      party ad networks. For example, you may go to the Digital Advertising
      Alliance (“DAA”) Consumer Choice Page
      at http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ for information about opting out
      of interest-based advertising and your choices regarding having
      information used by DAA companies. You may also go to the Network
      Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) Consumer Opt-Out Page
      at http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ for information about
      opting out of interest-based advertising and your choices regarding
      having information used by NAI members. Additional information is
      available on the DAA’s website at aboutads.info or the NAI’s website at
      www.networkadvertising.org. Opting out from one or more companies
      listed on the DAA Consumer Choice Page or the NAI Consumer Opt-
      Out Page will opt you out from those companies’ delivery of interest-
      based content or ads to you, but it does not mean you will no longer
      receive any advertising through our Services or any third-party services.
      You may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the

       particular website that you are viewing (i.e., contextually based ads). If
       your browser is configured to reject cookies when you opt out on the
       DAA or NAI websites, your opt out may not be effective. Please note
       that if you use multiple devices you will have to opt out on each
       individual device.
    •  Opting out of telemarketing. Where required by law, you will be
       contacted via telemarketing only with your consent. You may opt out of
       our direct telemarketing contacts by requesting us to remove you from
       our direct telemarking list. Please note that opting out from our direct
       telemarketing contacts does not limit us from contacting you for other
       purposes, including those contacts that are reasonably necessary to
       provide you with our Services. If you decide to opt out of our direct
       telemarketing contacts, allow a reasonable time for us to process your
       request and do not hesitate to contact us at privacy@3blmedia.com
       if you encounter any problems with your request.
    •  Accessing, updating or deleting your personal information. We
       value the accuracy of the information we have about you. You may
       access, update or delete your information (or in some cases object to its
       processing) at any time by emailing us at privacy@3blmedia.com.
Securing Your Personal Information
The security of your information is important to us, and we have
implemented administrative, technical, and physical safeguards designed to
protect personal information against theft or misuse. Unfortunately, no
system can guarantee complete security of your information. As a result,
while we strive to protect your personal information from unauthorized third
parties, 3BL Media cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information.
Thus, your use of the Services and communications with us is at your own
risk. You are responsible for protecting your username(s) and password(s) and
for the security of information that you transmit to us over the internet.
Children
Our Services are directed to working professionals. Our Services are not
intended for children under 13 years of age or the relevant age of majority,
and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under
that age. If you are under 13 years of age or the age of majority, you are not
permitted to submit any personal information to us.
Third-Party Information Collection
Like any business, we use service providers to operate our services, for
example such as website hosting, customer relationship databases and
systems. Some of these service providers will process your data as part of the
services they offer to us. We take steps to ensure that our service providers
treat your data in accordance with the law, only use it in accordance with our
contract with them and keep it secure.

Please note that these websites and services may have their own privacy
policies. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for the policies of any
third parties. If you chose to access any websites or services linked from our
Services, please check the applicable policies before you use or submit any
personal information to such website or service.
Third parties unaffiliated with us may also collect information about you,
including tracking your browsing history, when you use our Services. We do
not have control over these third-party collection practices and advise you to
adjust the settings of your browsers or install plug-ins and add-ins if you wish
to minimize these third party collections.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time to align with changes
to our business practices and/or changes to our legal requirements. We will
post the updated Privacy Policy on this page and will indicate that the
updates have been made by changing the effective date first written above.
We urge you to check back periodically to see whether there have been
updates to our Privacy Policy.
Your continued use of the Services or communication with us about the
Services after the updated Privacy Policy has been posted (or any other
indication of your consent) will constitute your acceptance of the updated
Privacy Policy.
Please note that we may condition your continued access to our Services on
your consent to changes to this Privacy Policy.
Personal Information Received from the EEA
3BL Media stores data about customers in the United States and we use
these central systems for the processing of your data. Any transfer of your
data will be carried out in accordance with the law, to safeguard your privacy
rights and in the unlikely event of a security breach, give you remedies, or any
other similar approved mechanisms. We will ensure that any transfer of your
personal data to the United States is done on the basis of EU Model Clauses
or on the basis of the Privacy Shield in order to achieve an adequate level of
data protection.
Personal information is transferred to 3BL Media, LLC in the US from the EU
under one of the following scenarios:
   •   Processor: 3BL Media, LLC is a provider of software, services and tools
       intended to help customers manage all aspects of their marketing and
       PR campaigns. 3BL Media, LLC does not own or control any of the
       information it processes on behalf of its customer. All such information
       is owned and controlled by 3BL Media, LLC’s customer. In this capacity,
       3BL Media, LLC receives information transferred from the EU to the US

       merely as a processor on behalf of its customer, although such
       information may not be required by 3BL Media, LLC.
    •  Data Controller: 3BL Media, LLC also provides information products
       designed to help customers shape, share and strategically target their
       campaigns more effectively. In this function, 3BL Media, LLC acts as a
       data controller of the personal information contained in these products
       and processes this personal information as described in this Policy in
       the US, a country that does not have the same level of protection for
       personal data as the EEA or Switzerland. 3BL Media, LLC maintains a
       media database containing personal information on EU contacts, and
       such individuals can have such information removed from our
       database. This information does not include sensitive information such
       as data about race, sexual orientation, or religion. This information is
       transferred to the US on the basis of consent, or European Commission-
       approved standard contractual clauses, and may be further transferred
       to our customers and to third party service providers located in Asia,
       Latin America and the Middle East, which do not have the same level of
       protection for personal data as the EEA or Switzerland, for the purposes
       described in this Policy.
3BL MEDIA, LLC TERMS OF USE AGREEMENT
The provisions of the 3BL Media, LLC Terms of Use Agreement are
incorporated into this Privacy Policy by reference with respect to all other
legal matters not otherwise addressed in this Privacy Policy. You should read
both this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use Agreement prior to review any
portion of our website and/or utilizing our Services.
Contact
If you have questions, comments or requests relating to this Privacy Policy, or
wish to opt out of any usage of your information as described herein, please
e-mail us at privacy@3blmedia.com or write to us at:
3BL Media, LLC
136 West St Ste 104
Northampton, MA 01060
